Homer Shantz Photograph Collection, 1904-1962 (bulk 1911-1958)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Unidentified Photographers
  - Subseries 1: Agave
    - Agave species beginning with D (Box 75, Tab 1)
    - Agave species beginning with E (Box 75, Tab 2)
    - Agave species beginning with F (Box 75, Tab 3)
    - Agave species beginning with G (Box 75, Tab 4)
    - Agave species beginning with H (Box 75, Tab 5)
    - Agave species beginning with I (Box 75, Tab 6)
    - Agave species beginning with J (Box 75, Tab 7)
    - Agave species beginning with K (Box 75, Tab 8)
    - Agave species beginning with L (Box 75, Tab 9)
    - Agave species beginning with M (Box 75, Tab 10)
    - Agave species beginning with N (Box 75, Tab 11)
    - Agave species beginning with O (Box 75, Tab 12)
    - Agave species beginning with P (Box 75, Tab 13)
    - Agave species beginning with R (Box 75, Tab 14)
    - Agave species beginning with S (Box 75, Tab 15)
    - Agave species beginning with T (Box 75, Tab 16)
    - Agave species beginning with U (Box 76, Tab 1)
    - Agave species beginning with V (Box 76, Tab 2)
    - Agave species beginning with W (Box 76, Tab 3)
    - Agave species beginning with X (Box 76, Tab 4)
    - Agave species beginning with Z (Box 76, Tab 5)
  - Subseries 2: Plants
    - Plant genera beginning with A (Box 76, Tab 6)
    - Plant genera beginning with B (Box 76, Tab 7)
    - Plant genera beginning with C (Box 76, Tab 8)
    - Plant genera beginning with D (Box 76, Tab 9)
    - Plant genera beginning with E (Box 76, Tab 10)
    - Plant genera beginning with F (Box 76, Tab 11)
    - Plant genera beginning with G (Box 76, Tab 12)
    - Plant genera beginning with H (Box 76, Tab 13)
    - Plant genera beginning with J (Box 76, Tab 14)
    - Plant genera beginning with L (Box 76, Tab 15)
    - Plant genera beginning with M (Box 76, Tab 16)
    - Plant genera beginning with N (Box 76, Tab 17)
    - Plant genera beginning with O (Box 76, Tab 18)
    - Plant genera beginning with P (Box 76, Tab 19)
    - Plant genera beginning with R (Box 76, Tab 20)
    - Plant genera beginning with S (Box 76, Tab 21)
    - Plant genera beginning with T (Box 76, Tab 22)
    - Plant genera beginning with Y (Box 76, Tab 23)
  - Subseries 3: Specimens
    - Specimens of plant genera A (Box 76, Tab 24)
    - Specimens of plant genera B (Box 76, Tab 25)
    - Specimens of plant genera C (Box 76, Tab 26)
    - Specimens of plant genera D (Box 76, Tab 27)
    - Specimens of plant genera E (Box 76, Tab 28)
    - Specimens of plant genera H (Box 76, Tab 29)
    - Specimens of plant genera M (Box 76, Tab 30)
    - Specimens of plant genera O (Box 76, Tab 31)
    - Specimens of plant genera P (Box 76, Tab 32)
    - Specimens of plant genera S (Box 76, Tab 33)
    - Specimens of plant genera T (Box 76, Tab 34)
    - Specimens of plant genera Y (Box 76, Tab 35)
    - Specimens of plant genera Z (Box 76, Tab 36)
  - Subseries 4: Various Locations
    - Africa, Archers Post (Box 77, Tab 1)
    - Africa, Bukuma (Box 77, Tab 2)
    - Africa, Butiaba (Box 77, Tab 3)
    - Africa, Cape Province (Box 77, Tab 4)
    - Africa, De Doorns (Box 77, Tab 5)
    - Africa, Kauro (Box 77, Tab 6)
    - Africa, Kigoma (Box 77, Tab 7)
    - Africa, Kindu (Box 77, Tab 8)
    - Africa, Lurenҫo Marques (Box 77, Tab 9)
    - Africa, Livingstonia Waterfall (Box 77, Tab 10)
    - Africa, Lulaba River (Box 77, Tab 11)
    - Africa, Mahagi-Port (Box 77, Tab 12)
    - Africa, Monkey Bay (Box 77, Tab 13)
    - Africa, Palm Grove (Box 77, Tab 14)
    - Africa, Ujiji (Box 77, Tab 15)
    - Africa, Thika Falls (Box 77, Tab 16)
    - Arizona, Baboquivari Park (Box 77, Tab 17)
    - Arizona, Big Lake (Box 77, Tab 18)
    - Arizona, Escudilla Mountains (Box 77, Tab 19)
    - Arizona, Flagstaff, Fort Valley Ranch (Box 77, Tab 20)
    - Arizona, Grand Canyon (Box 77, Tab 21)
    - Arizona, Kayenta (Box 77, Tab 22)
    - Arizona, Santa Catalina Mountains (Box 77, Tab 23)
    - Arizona, Santa Rita Mountains (Box 77, Tab 24)
    - Arizona, Sonoita Creek (Box 77, Tab 25)
    - Arizona, Superstition Mountains (Box 77, Tab 26)
    - Arizona, University of Arizona (Box 77, Tab 27)
    - Arizona, White Mountains (Box 77, Tab 28)
    - Baja California, Bahia de Los Angeles (Box 77, Tab 29)
    - Baja California, Isla San Marcos (Box 77, Tab 30)
    - Baja California, La Paz (Box 77, Tab 31)
    - Baja California, Llano Dirai (Box 77, Tab 32)
    - Baja California, Mina Desengana (Box 77, Tab 33)
    - Baja California, Mission San Xavier (Box 77, Tab 34)
    - California, Golf Region Vegetation (Box 77, Tab 35)
    - California, Murrieta (Box 77, Tab 36)
    - Central America (Box 77, Tab 37)
    - Chihuahua, Casas Grandes (Box 77, Tab 38)
    - Colorado, Monument Valley (Box 77, Tab 39)
    - Colorado, Rocky Mountain National Park (Box 77, Tab 40)
    - Costa Rica, Alajuela (Box 77, Tab 41)
    - Durango Grasslands (Box 77, Tab 42)
    - Guatemala, Coban (Box 77, Tab 43)
    - Guatemala, Izabal (Box 77, Tab 44)
    - Guatemala, Nahualate (Box 77, Tab 45)
    - Guerro, Canyon Igula (Box 77, Tab 46)
    - Honduras, Zamorano (Box 77, Tab 47)
    - Mexico, Rosario (Box 77, Tab 48)
    - Mexico, Uruapan (Box 77, Tab 49)
    - Monterrey, Canyon Huasteca (Box 77, Tab 50)
    - Nayarit, Acaponeta (Box 77, Tab 51)
    - North Dakota, Painted Canyon (Box 77, Tab 52)
    - Oaxaca (Box 77, Tab 53)
    - Oaxaca, Sierra Mahuizapam (Box 77, Tab 54)
    - Oregon, Crater Lake (Box 77, Tab 55)
    - Road to Ruby from Nogales (Box 77, Tab 56)
    - Wyoming, String Lake (Box 77, Tab 57)
    - San Juan River (Box 77, Tab 58)
    - Sierra de las Palmas (Box 77, Tab 59)
    - Sinaloa, Cerro Babuyo (Box 77, Tab 60)
    - Sinaloa, Esquinapa (Box 77, Tab 61)
    - Sonora, Alamos (Box 77, Tab 62)
    - Sonora, Cedros Range (Box 77, Tab 63)
    - Sonora, San Bernardo (Box 77, Tab 64)
    - Sonora, San Pedro Nolasco Island (Box 77, Tab 65)
    - South Dakota, Mount Rushmore (Box 77, Tab 66)
    - Turkey, Izmir (Box 77, Tab 67)
    - Unidentified locations (Box 77, Tab 68)
    - Utah, Bryce Canyon (Box 77, Tab 69)
    - Utah, Navajo Mountain (Box 77, Tab 70)
    - Wyoming, Devils Tower (Box 77, Tab 71)
    - Yosemite National Park (Box 77, Tab 72)
- Series VII: Card Catalog
  This series contain two card catalogs. Original order of the catalogs has been maintained.
  - Acrostichum to Diplazium (Box 78)
  - Dryopteris to Pilularia (Box 79)
  - Tab 1 Pityrogramma to Ferns (Box 80, Tab 1)
  - Adiantum capillus-veneris to Asplenium palmeri (Box 80, Tab 2)
  - Asplenium resiliens to Noth. Grayi (Box 81)
  - Noth. Interrima to Woodwardia fimbriata (Box 82)
- Series VIII: Oversize materials
  This series contains oversize photographs. It is divided into 4 subseries and is organized alphabetically.
  - Subseries 1: Environmental Comparison
    - Arizona, Oracle and Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 1)
    - Arizona, Santa Rita Range (Box 83, Plate 2)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 3)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 4)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 5)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 6)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 7)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 8)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 9)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 10)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 11)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 12)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 13)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 14)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 15)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 16)
    - Arizona, Saguaro National Park (Box 83, Plate 17)
    - Cactoblastis Cantorum attack (Box 83, Plate 18)
    - Colorado, Huerfano Butte (Box 83, Plate 19)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 20)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 21)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 22)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 23)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 24)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 25)
    - Montana, Danvers (Box 83, Plate 26)
    - Montana, Fairview (Box 83, Plate 27)
    - Montana, Forsyth (Box 83, Plate 28)
    - Montana, Gardiner (Box 83, Plate 29)
    - Montana, Grassrange (Box 83, Plate 30)
    - Montana, Grassrange (Box 83, Plate 31)
    - Montana, Harve (Box 83, Plate 32)
    - Montana, Harve (Box 83, Plate 33)
    - Montana, Lewiston (Box 83, Plate 34)
    - Montana, Lewiston (Box 83, Plate 35)
    - Montana, Lewiston (Box 83, Plate 36)
    - Montana, Lewiston (Box 83, Plate 37)
    - Montana, Lewiston (Box 83, Plate 38)
    - Montana, Lewiston (Box 83, Plate 39)
    - Montana, Lombard (Box 83, Plate 40)
    - Montana, Moccasin (Box 83, Plate 41)
    - Montana, Roundup (Box 83, Plate 42)
    - Montana, Roundup (Box 83, Plate 43)
    - Montana, Townsend (Box 83, Plate 44)
    - Montana, Townsend (Box 83, Plate 45)
    - Montana, Valentine (Box 84, Plate 1)
    - Montana, Valentine (Box 84, Plate 2)
    - Montana, Valentine (Box 84, Plate 3)
    - Nebraska, Crawford (Box 84, Plate 4)
    - Nebraska, Long Pine (Box 84, Plate 5)
    - Nebraska, Sydney (Box 84, Plate 6)
    - North Dakota, Fort Lincoln (Box 84, Plate 7)
    - North Dakota, Fryburg (Box 84, Plate 8)
    - North Dakota, Fryburg (Box 84, Plate 9)
    - North Dakota, Fryburg (Box 84, Plate 10)
    - North Dakota, Fryburg (Box 84, Plate 11)
    - North Dakota, Fryburg (Box 84, Plate 12)
    - North Dakota, Hettinger (Box 84, Plate 13)
    - North Dakota, Hettinger (Box 84, Plate 14)
    - North Dakota, Mandan (Box 84, Plate 15)
    - North Dakota, Mandan (Box 84, Plate 16)
    - North Dakota, Mandan (Box 84, Plate 17)
    - North Dakota, Mandan (Box 84, Plate 18)
    - North Dakota, Mandan (Box 84, Plate 19)
    - North Dakota, Scranton (Box 84, Plate 20)
    - South Dakota, Arpan (Box 84, Plate 21)
    - South Dakota, Bellefourche (Box 84, Plate 22)
    - South Dakota, Belvidere (Box 84, Plate 23)
    - South Dakota, Belvidere (Box 84, Plate 24)
    - South Dakota, Belvidere (Box 84, Plate 25)
    - South Dakota, Belvidere (Box 84, Plate 26)
    - South Dakota, Belvidere (Box 84, Plate 27)
    - South Dakota, Blunt (Box 84, Plate 28)
    - South Dakota, Blunt (Box 84, Plate 29)
    - South Dakota, Custer State Park (Box 84, Plate 30)
    - South Dakota, Custer State Park (Box 84, Plate 31)
    - South Dakota, Deadwood (Box 84, Plate 32)
    - South Dakota, Deadwood (Box 84, Plate 33)
    - South Dakota, Fort Pierre (Box 84, Plate 34)
    - South Dakota, Gregory (Box 84, Plate 35)
    - South Dakota, Highmore (Box 84, Plate 36)
    - South Dakota, Highmore (Box 84, Plate 37)
    - South Dakota, Hot Springs (Box 84, Plate 38)
    - South Dakota, Hot Springs (Box 84, Plate 39)
    - South Dakota, Hot Springs (Box 84, Plate 40)
    - South Dakota, Kadoka (Box 84, Plate 41)
    - South Dakota, Kadoka (Box 84, Plate 42)
    - South Dakota, Kadoka (Box 84, Plate 43)
    - South Dakota, Kadoka (Box 84, Plate 44)
    - South Dakota, Newell (Box 84, Plate 45)
    - South Dakota, Newell (Box 84, Plate 46)
    - South Dakota, Pineridge (Box 84, Plate 47)
    - South Dakota, Redfield (Box 84, Plate 48)
    - South Dakota, Rosebud (Box 84, Plate 49)
    - South Dakota, Rumford (Box 84, Plate 50)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 84, Plate 51)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 84, Plate 52)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 85, Plate 1)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 85, Plate 2)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 85, Plate 3)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 85, Plate 4)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 85, Plate 5)
    - South Dakota, Spearfish (Box 85, Plate 6)
    - South Dakota, Sturgis (Box 85, Plate 7)
    - South Dakota, Timberlake (Box 85, Plate 8)
    - South Dakota, Timberlake (Box 85, Plate 9)
    - South Dakota, Timberlake (Box 85, Plate 10)
    - South Dakota, Whiteriver (Box 85, Plate 11)
    - South Dakota, Whitewood (Box 85, Plate 12)
    - South Dakota, Whitewood (Box 85, Plate 13)
    - South Dakota, Whitewood (Box 85, Plate 14)
    - South Dakota, Wounded Knee (Box 85, Plate 15)
    - South Dakota, Wounded Knee (Box 85, Plate 16)
    - Wyoming, Buffalo (Box 85, Plate 17)
    - Wyoming, Buffalo (Box 85, Plate 18)
    - Wyoming, Casper (Box 85, Plate 19)
    - Wyoming, Casper (Box 85, Plate 20)
    - Wyoming, Casper (Box 85, Plate 21)
    - Wyoming, Casper (Box 85, Plate 22)
    - Wyoming, Casper (Box 85, Plate 23)
    - Wyoming, Cody (Box 85, Plate 24)
    - Wyoming, Cody (Box 85, Plate 25)
    - Wyoming, Crazy Women Creek (Box 85, Plate 26)
    - Wyoming, Crazy Women Creek (Box 85, Plate 27)
    - Wyoming, Crazy Women Creek (Box 85, Plate 28)
    - Wyoming, Devils Tower (Box 85, Plate 29)
    - Wyoming, Grand Tenton (Box 85, Plate 30)
    - Wyoming, Hulett (Box 85, Plate 31)
    - Wyoming, Hulett (Box 85, Plate 32)
    - Wyoming, Story (Box 85, Plate 33)
    - Wyoming, Story (Box 85, Plate 34)
    - Wyoming, Story (Box 85, Plate 35)
    - Wyoming, Story (Box 85, Plate 36)
    - Wyoming, Story (Box 85, Plate 37)
    - Wyoming, Story (Box 85, Plate 38)
    - Wyoming, Sundance (Box 85, Plate 39)
    - Wyoming, Ten sleep (Box 85, Plate 40)
    - Wyoming, Ten sleep (Box 85, Plate 41)
    - Wyoming, Thermopolis (Box 85, Plate 42)
  - Subseries 2: Walter Phillips oversize materials
    - Diagram of grass types (Box 86, Plate 1)
    - Popular Photography article, 1943 (Box 86, Plate 2)
    - Popular Photography article, 1946 (Box 86, Plate 3)
    - Unidentified topography photographs (Box 86, Plate 4)
    - University of Arizona Botany Lab (Box 86, Plate 5)
  - Subseries 3: Identified Landscapes
    - Florida, Flamingo (Box 86, Plate 6)
    - Florida, Homosassa Springs (Box 86, Plate 7)
    - Nevada, Virgin Mountains (Box 86, Plate 8)
    - New York, Canandaigua Lake (Box 86, Plate 9)
    - Utah, Bryce Canyon (Box 86, Plate 10)
  - Subseries 4: Various prints
    - Various prints (Box 86, Plate 11-39)